capacity tonight here at the opulent
Tostitos Center 50,000 fans are ready to
binge drink for a couple of hours I tell
you what I can't wait hot I'm thrilled
Med ship Sarika then I'm grown man Bob
to say to you that's right Bob and we
have both made careers watching adult
men play a simple child's game all will
be paid more than the president okay
chick and it seems as though the
millionaires are ready to play their
game so we can stop stalling with the
mindless Chad the Rhinos bring the ball
to play and the alleged rapist passes
the big orange ball to the sweaty legal
giant easily puts the ball into the
basket making it look easy which victory
seven feet tall it is he made about
$8,000 while he was doing now the power
of Falcons are bringing the ball into
play the high school dropout inbounds to
the convicted spousal abuse er he
slashes through all of the drug addict
stops the ball to the genetic freak boom
quack the lack of cue points don't ask
your black ass bingo times derm scabs
[Music]
just saying words and start with this
[Laughter]
[Applause]
great